<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer Series on String Phenomenology</title>
    <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Summer Series on String Phenomenology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/schedule/</guid>
      <description>The talk series will be held via Zoom from 11:00AM-12:00PM EDT on Tuesdays. Please register to the mailing list to receive the links.
The schedule of upcoming talks is as follows:
Tuesday, September 8, 2020   11:00, Craig Lawrie, Penn
  11:30, Manki Kim, Cornell
  Tuesday, September 15, 2020   11:00, Pierre Corvilain, IFT Madrid
  11:30, Igor Broeckel, Bologna
  Tuesday, September 22, 2020   11:00, Mehmet Demirtas, Cornell</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Talks</title>
      <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/past-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/past-talks/</guid>
      <description>All talk videos can be found here. See below for individual talk information, slides, and video links.
Tuesday, September 1, 2020  11:00, Gregory Joseph Loges, UW Madison  Title: Weak Gravity and Dualities
Abstract: The mild form of the Weak Gravity Conjecture requires that the charge-to-mass ratio of extremal black holes is shifted to be larger than one. In 4D Einstein-Maxwell theory, much mileage is gained in understanding the effect of higher derivative terms in the effective action along with principles such as unitarity of scattering amplitudes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register</title>
      <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/registration/</guid>
      <description>To be added to the mailing list please register.
If you are interested in giving a talk please fill out the form here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>This seminar series is designed to highlight the work of theorists early in their careers, in the broad topic of String Phenomenology. The talks are held virtually on Tuesdays, from 11 AM - 12 PM EST, in order to allow for maximum participation across the globe. All presentations will be by junior researchers who are not yet in permanent positions.
Talks will be given via Zoom. Please register to the mailing list to receive the links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stringphenoseminars.github.io/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright (c) 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>